Nguyen Tat Toan

Unit36, 28th Floor, CT12C Building, Nghiem Xuan Yem, Dai Kim

Hoang Mai, Hanoi, Vietnam

Tel: +84 903 050 020

Email: toannguyenata18@gmail.com

Website: https://toannguyentat.com

Hanoi, 02 November 2022

Letter of Application

Dear Hiring Managers,

I would like to introduce myself, my name is Nguyen Tat Toan and I am living with family in Hanoi.

I am a full stack developer with some technologies like C#, python, kotlin, javascript, php and some frameworks supporting these above languages like Django, React, .NET core, ASP.NET core, Android Studio.

I have done with databases like MySQL, PostgreSQL and Oracle SQL and I use RESTful Api.

I can build applications running on desktop, windows, web and android, or I can customize existing source code applications for new functionalities as requested.

I improve knowledge and skills by doing self-taught, and I usually use tools like youtube or internet tutorials for updating new emerging technologies and information.

I am very interested in technologies and programming language. And I am very happy to be joined in a team or worked independently in your company, to contribute a part to company's success in coming time.

And I did attach below my CV for your consideration, I am available for an interview in your spare time.

Yours Sincerely,

Nguyen Tat Toan (Mr.)

Nguyen Tat Toan

Full Stack Developer



Personal Information

Address: Hoang Mai, Hanoi, Vietnam

Phone: +84 0903 050 020

Email: toannguyentat18@gmail.com

Website: https://toannguyentat.com

Language & Database & Concept

- OOPs, Python, PHP, Kotlin, C#, Java
- HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT,
- PostgreSQL, MYSQL, Oracle Database

Framework & Library & API

- Django, PyQT5, OpenCV, BOOSTRAP
- · Android Studio, ReactJS, Sanity.io
- Retrofit, Volley
- ASP.NET & .NET Core
- RESTful API

IDE & Build tools & Pattern

- Gradle, Android Studio, Visual Studio
- Visual Code, PyCharm
- MVVM, MVC, MVP

Education

Military Technical Academy

Degree in Electronics/Electricity

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Degree in Electronics/Electrical Equipment

"Full Stack Developer with skill and knowledge on Java, C#, Python, Kotlin, JavaScript and related frameworks"

Experience

Phuc Binh Technology Company (June 2019 - Present)

Full Stack Developer

As a full stack developer, I build apps for frontend and backend with technologies, libraries and frameworks as I listed above.

I build apps for desktop, windows, web and android. I can create new app, or I can customize existing app for further purpose.

So far, I have joined some projects as described below.

<u>Project 1</u>: Monitor **student by f**ace recognition and notify on android app to student's parent when she/he was absent at class.

- ✓ Language : Python, Kotlin, C#
- ✓ Tool: Visual Studio Code, Android Studio
- ✓ Framework: Django, Android, PyQT5, .NET Core
- ✓ Server: IIS, AWS
- ✓ Database: PostgreSQL
- ✓ API: RESTful

<u>Project 2</u>: Intrusion detection by applying deep learning to detect human and alarm on screen, notify on android app to household.

- ✓ Language: Python, Kotlin
- ✓ Tool: PyCharm, Visual Studio Code, Android Studio
- ✓ Framework: Django, PyQT5, Android Studio
- ✓ Server: IIS
- ✓ Database: MySQL

<u>Project 3:</u> Wi-Fi marketing by doing authentication on remote server for the goal of advertisement to client.

- ✓ Language: PHP
- ✓ Tool: Visual Studio, Notepad
- √ Framework: WIFI Dog
- ✓ Server: IIS
- Database: MySQL

ANZ Bank (Vietnam) Limited (Dec 2009 – Jan 2018)

Technical Officer

As a technical officer, my jobs are described as follows:

- ✓ In charge of monitoring the leased line communication
- Create tools to monitor status of ATM system
- ✓ Create tools to analyze customer transaction data error on journal roll
- Coordinate ATM team as well as partners and security
- Collaborate with ANZ overseas technical team to perform new functionalities for bank system
- Customer service related to technical problem on bank system
- ✓ Report and scheduling

Ability

- Work independently or in a teamwork
- Ability to work in pressured environment
- Adapt quickly to new change as require
- Ability to learn new thing fast
- Project management
- Time management
- English fluency

VISCO Joint Stock Company (May 2005 – Dec 2009)

Project Officer

As a project officer I had to take care of company's project in northern of Vietnam. Collaborate with Southern team and overseas team as well to complete project. Details of jobs as below:

- ✓ Presale to customer new product and keep updated information relating to project
- ✓ Team management on schedule of installation
- √ Time management on deadline as well as issue emerge
- ✓ Project supervisor takes care of testing and commissioning.
- ✓ Responsibility for training technology to customer.
- ✓ Report and paperwork on project completed

Union for Science of Electronic Engineering (1998 – 2003) SEEN Company Ltd.

Technical Officer

I was responsible for management an electronic assembling production line that consist of 9 workers.

- ✓ Organized printed circuit board assembling and testing
- ✓ Programming and customizing firmware for Microcontroller 8051 families on demand for each project
- ✓ Firmware testing bases on actual product hardware
- ✓ In charge of installation and test and commissioning to customer in northern of Vietnam